Brandi N Peters

678-203-5404 petersbn@gmail.com brandi-n-peters in bnicp

SUMMARY

Resourceful, reliable, hard-working professional with 10+ years successful remote work roles. Knowledgeable across multiple industries and has leadership and management experience with direct reports. Excellent with new technologies and a quick learner of software and processes. Customer centric, treating everyone with empathy and respect.



EXPERIENCE

Systems Consultant | Beep Co, LLC - Alpharetta, GA

2020-Present

- Consults with RE agents and clients on the systems they have in place for business efficiency
- Recommends technologies to implement for automation so they can focus on sales
- Includes training on new systems, integration, and custom business website builds

Systems Coach | LOCAL Realty / Red Barn Real Estate

2019-2021

- Conducted new agent onboarding, systems input, and user account creation
- Administrator for all company technology, including Google Workspace
- Consulted with agents about the individual systems in place for their personal sales businesses

Manager, Collections | Previously- Collections Team Lead, Asset Manager, Asset Performance Specialist | CAN Capital, Inc. - Kennesaw, GA 2015 - 2018

- Partnered with business analytics on SSRS reporting to achieve streamlined processes
- Coordinated with IT to verify root causes of system errors and tested bug fixes
- Oversaw a portfolio in excess of \$20,000,000 worked by 3-5 agents
- Executed cost analysis for under performing assets and forecasted monthly revenue and loss

Web Content Creator | Proxy Server, LLC - Remote, GA

2014

- Created and curated content for math curriculum and social sharing sites
- Wrote and implemented multi-level curriculum and FAQs
- Utilized HTML for formatting and presentation on each Wordpress page



RECENT WEB PROJECTS

geek connect | 2022

Wrote HTML5/CSS3 to design "geek connect," a site for geeks to find each other based on common interests in fantasy worlds. Link to GitHub repository: https://github.com/bnicp/geek-connect

FDA Recalls Near Me

2022

Contributed HTML and CSS framework (W3.CSS) to a site for consumers to retrieve information regarding FDA recalls. Link to GitHub repository: https://github.com/bnicp/recall-near-me

Password Generator | 2022

Web app to generate strong and random passwords with multiple parameter options. Link to GitHub repository: https://github.com/bnicp/password-generator

JavaScript Quiz | 2022

Quiz app with easily editable questions. Alerts correct or incorrect answers and stores high scores. Link to GitHub repository: https://github.com/bnicp/javascript-quiz



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts in Business Administration | University of Florida, 2004



SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Cross-functional Collaboration
- HTML5
- Bootstrap
- Git
- Github

- Process Innovation
- Training
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Zendesk
- Heroku